[{"answer": "We can't drop it now, my friend. We bought the land around this Dam and we're holding it in dummy names. If we drop it or delay i", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Don't worry about my frien", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "*my friend", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "We can't help", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Than what", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " my friend! Will you", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Oh, no", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yes, my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "U", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Th", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Even to the hat. Same old dreamer, too. One look at you and I can see him, back of his old roll top desk, hat and all, getting out his paper. Always kept his hat on his head so as to be ready to do battle. my friend, editor and publisher, and champion of lost causes", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You don't have to tell me my friend. We were a team, the two of us, a struggling editor and a struggling lawyer. The twin champions of lost causes, they used to call us", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Ge", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Pleased to meet you, sir", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Pleased to meet you, sir", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Made it? Oh! Yes. Silly of m", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " With or without 'em.  Twelv", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " No. What had you bette", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Ax", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Wel", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Senator my friend", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Is there objection?  The journal stands approved", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "That's all right, my bo", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Good as new! It's quite all righ", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Wel", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Goodnight, Miss my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I had a lot to do with that little press conference last nigh", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "We're going right ahead wit", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Fine. Now, what does he do? He's got to sit down first and write it up. The where, when, why, ho", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I see.", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Tonight.  Loo", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "U", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You get to your feet in the that place and present it. Then you take the my friend and put it in a little bo", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Committee", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "A committee of the majority party leaders. They decide when a Bill is important enough to be moved up toward the head of the lis", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Pardon m", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Have I", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I don't see where we are", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "The Silver Knight. Soul of Hono", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You pla", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "U", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "That'", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well, what do you want me to do? Stand around like you chump and let that drooling infant wrap that my friend appropriation around my neck. Either he falls in line with us and behaves himself or I'll break him so wide open they'll never be able to find the pieces", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "You won't stand for it", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " Just a minute, my friend", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "*", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " It might save some of the pieces, my friend. It would leave a doubt about the whole thin", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": " Well, I guess it's a chance", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " Well, I guess it's a chance", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": " I", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Wai", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Bu", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "And Senator my friend too, M", "docId": "MrSmithGoesToWashington.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "How's my friend, my friend", "qsentId": 54}]